A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 3: Correspondence
  - Subseries 19: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930
    - Miscellaneous - S, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1187)
    - H.S. Seward, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1188)
    - William H. Stauffer, 1930-1932 (Box-folder 15-1189)
    - Edward L. Stone, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1190)
    - Miscellaneous - T, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1191)
    - Miscellaneous - U, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1192)
    - U.S. Chamber of Commerce - E.W. Cullough, etc., 1930 (Box-folder 15-1193)
    - Virginia Economic & Civic, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1194)
    - Virginia Manufacturer's Association (Box-folder 15-1195)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1196)
    - Miscellaneous - W, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1197)
    - T. Gilbert Wood, 1930 (Box-folder 15-1198)
  - Subseries 20: Faculty Correspondence, 1931
    - Barlow, Begg (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 15-1199)
    - Brown, Burkhart (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 15-1200)
    - Cowgill, Cunningham (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 15-1201)
    - Dinwiddie, Martha - women students (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 15-1202)
    - Drinkard (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 15-1203)
    - Ellis, W. T. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1204)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1205)
    - Fogleman (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1206)
    - Garnett, W. E. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1207)
    - Godkin, Grenoble (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1208)
    - Holdaway, C. W. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1209)
    - Holden, R. J. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1210)
    - Hubert, Reuben L. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1211)
    - Hummel, Hunt (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1212)
    - Hutcheson, John R. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1213)
    - Hutcheson, T. B. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1214)
    - Johnson, J. S. A. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1215)
    - Knote, T. W. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1216)
    - Lodewick, Lucas, J. B. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1217)
    - Maynard, John B. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1218)
    - McNeil, R. H. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1219)
    - Michael, R. D. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1220)
    - Miles, C.P. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1221)
    - Miller, E. C. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1222)
    - Norris, E. B. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1223)
    - Norton, Paul T. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1224)
    - O'Shaughnessy (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1225)
    - Owens, J.J. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1226)
    - Price, H.L. (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1227)
    - Sette, F. J. - water and sewage issues (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1228)
    - Seitz (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1229)
    - Watson, J.W.; Williams, J. E.; Woolwine (Faculty Correspondence), 1931 (Box-folder 16-1230)
  - Subseries 21: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1931
    - Miscellaneous A-B, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1231)
    - H.K. Bowen, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1232)
    - J.H. Bradford, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1233)
    - Miscellaneous C-D, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1234)
    - Westmoreland Davis, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1235)
    - Paul N. Derring, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1236)
    - Miscellaneous E-I, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1237)
    - Miscellaneous J-M, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1238)
    - Miscellaneous N-P, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1239)
    - Lawrence Priddy, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1240)
    - Gov. J.G. Pollard, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1241)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1242)
    - D.G. Robson, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1243)
    - Miscellaneous S-T, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1244)
    - Miscellaneous W-Z, 1931 (Box-folder 16-1245)
  - Subseries 22: Faculty Correspondence, 1932
    - Begg, R. B.H. (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1246)
    - Brown, R.M. (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1247)
    - Chaplains (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1248)
    - Cowgill (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1249)
    - A.W. Drinkard (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1250)
    - Eaff, Ellis (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1251)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1252)
    - Fogleman, Garnett, Gudheim (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1253)
    - M.C. Harrison, W.T. Hartman (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1254)
    - Holdaway (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1255)
    - R.J. Holden, R.L. Humbert (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 12-1256)
    - B.L. Hummel, R.E. Hunt (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1257)
    - J.R. Hutcheson, T.B. Hutcheson (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1258)
    - Jefferies, Knote (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1259)
    - V.E. Kelsey, J.B. Lucas (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1260)
    - R. H. McNeil (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1261)
    - E.G. Magill (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1262)
    - Mahaney, J.P. (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1263)
    - Maynard, J. B. - Corps of Cadets (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1264)
    - Michael (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1265)
    - C.P. Miles (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1266)
    - E.C. Miller (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1267)
    - Minter, Montgomery (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1268)
    - E.B. Norris (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1269)
    - C.M. Newman (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1270)
    - O'Shaughnessy (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1271)
    - H.L. Price (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1272)
    - S.R. Pritchard, W.H. Rasche (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1273)
    - Redd, H. B., Alumni Association - Women Student Stats (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1274)
    - Scherer, Seitz, Sette (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1275)
    - J.W. Watson (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1276)
    - J.E. Williams, I.D. Wilson, H.N. Young (Faculty Correspondence), 1932 (Box-folder 16-1277)
  - Subseries 23: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1932
    - Miscellaneous - A, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1278)
      - Norfolk & Western Railway relations with VPI
    - Miscellaneous - B, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1279)
      - Alpha Zeta Chapter establishment
      - Richmond Symphony Orchestra
      - George Washington School House dedication
      - Motto of America and George Washington
    - Hon. J. Gordon Bohannon, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1280)
      - Bill for the Merchant Marine Training School
      - Nautical School bill
    - H. K. Bowen, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1281)
    - J. H. Bradford, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1282)
    - Miscellaneous C-D, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1283)
      - Radio station WEHC
    - Paul N. Derring, 1932 (Box-folder 16-1284)
      - Report to the President concerning the YMCA
    - Miscellaneous - E, F, G, 1932 (Box-folder 17-1285)
      - State nautical school
      - Improvement of water supply by the college
    - Miscellaneous - H, 1932 (Box-folder 17-1286)
    - Miscellaneous - I, J, 1932 (Box-folder 17-1287)
    - J. Ambler Johnston, 1932 (Box-folder 17-1288)
    - Miscellaneous - K (Box-folder 17-1289)
      - Opposition to radio broadcast of Southern Conference football games
      - Inauguration of King College president, Bristol, Tennessee
    - Miscellaneous - L (Box-folder 17-1290)
      - Organization of Mu Omega Xi National Scholarship Fraternity
    - Miscellaneous - M (Box-folder 17-1291)
    - J. P. McConnell (Box-folder 17-1292)
    - Manufacturer's bluebook (Box-folder 17-1293)
    - Miscellaneous - N, O (Box-folder 17-1294)
    - Miscellaneous P (Box-folder 17-1295)
    - Governor J. G. Pollard (Box-folder 17-1296)
    - Miscellaneous - Q, R (Box-folder 17-1297)
    - D. G. Robson (Box-folder 17-1298)
    - Miscellaneous - S (Box-folder 17-1299)
    - W. T. Sanger (Box-folder 17-1300)
    - Edward L. Stone (Box-folder 17-1301)
    - Miscellaneous - T, V, W (Box-folder 17-1302)
    - War Department (Box-folder 17-1303)
    - C. A. Woodrum (Box-folder 17-1304)
    - Miscellaneous - X, Y, Z (Box-folder 17-1305)
    - H. H. Zimmerley (Box-folder 17-1306)
  - Subseries 24: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933
    - Miscellaneous A-C, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1307)
      - Annual Report to Federal Board for Vocational Education Teacher Training for Whites Only
      - Proposed changes to animal husbandry
    - Miscellaneous D, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1308)
    - Derring, Paul N., 1933 (Box-folder 17-1309)
    - Miscellaneous E-F, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1310)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1311)
    - A. B. Gathright, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1312)
    - Miscellaneous H-J, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1313)
    - J. Ambler Johnston, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1314)
    - Miscellaneous K, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1315)
    - George W. Koiner, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1316)
    - Miscellaneous L-M, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1317)
      - Constitution of the Lord Reading Club for Hebrew students
      - Sale of beer at the college bookstore
    - J. P. McConnell, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1318)
    - Miscellaneous N-P, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1319)
    - Governor J. G. Pollard, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1320)
    - Lawrence Priddy, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1321)
    - Miscellaneous R-S, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1322)
    - Wm. T. Sanger, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1323)
    - Miscellaneous T-W, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1324)
    - War Department, 1933 (Box-folder 18-1325)
    - C.A. Woodrum, 1933 (Box-folder 18-1326)
    - Miscellaneous Y, 1933 (Box-folder 18-1327)
    - H.H. Zimmerley, 1933 (Box-folder 17-1328)
  - Subseries 25: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1934-1936
    - Miscellaneous A, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1329)
    - Miscellaneous B, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1330)
    - G.T. Baird (Box-folder 18-1331)
    - T. Boyd, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1332)
    - R.M. Brown (Box-folder 18-1333)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1334)
    - Cuthnell, Milton (Box-folder 18-1335)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1336)
    - P. Derring (Box-folder 18-1337)
    - A.W. Drinkard (Box-folder 18-1338)
    - Miscellaneous E, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1339)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1340)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters (Box-folder 18-1341)
    - Financial Statements (Box-folder 18-1342)
    - J. B. Fogelman (Box-folder 18-1343)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1344)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1345)
    - C. W. Holdaway (Box-folder 18-1346)
    - R. J. Holden (Box-folder 18-1347)
    - R. L. Humbert (Box-folder 18-1348)
    - J.R. Hutcheson (Box-folder 18-1349)
    - C. J. Hyslup (Box-folder 18-1350)
    - Miscellaneous J-K, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1351)
    - W. Koiner (Box-folder 18-1352)
    - Miscellaneous L, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1353)
    - Chas. Lumford and Sons (Box-folder 18-1354)
    - Miscellaneous M, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1355)
    - E. C. Magill (Box-folder 18-1356)
    - C. P. Miles (Box-folder 18-1357)
    - E. C. Miller (Box-folder 18-1358)
    - H. L. Moore (Box-folder 18-1359)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 18-1360)
    - E. B. Norris (2 folders) (Box-folder 18-1361 and 18-1361A)
    - Miscellaneous O, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1362)
    - O'Shaughnessey (Box-folder 19-1363)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1364)
    - George C. Peery, Governor, 1934 (Box-folder 19-1365)
      - Student Financial Aid and College Funding.
      - Dovell Proposal to cut Special Funding by 15%.
    - Miscellaneous R, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1366)
    - W. H. Rasche (Box-folder 19-1367)
    - H B. Redd (Box-folder 19-1368)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1369)
    - Sanger, W. T. (Box-folder 19-1370)
    - C. Seitz (Box-folder 19-1371)
    - Miscellaneous T, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1372)
    - C. H. Tenney (Box-folder 19-1373)
    - Miscellaneous V, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1374)
    - B. H. Van Oot (Box-folder 19-1375)
    - F. C. Vilbrandt (Box-folder 19-1376)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1377)
    - J. W. Watson (Box-folder 19-1378)
    - J. E. Williams (Box-folder 19-1379)
    - I. D. Wilson (Box-folder 19-1380)
    - Miscellaneous Y, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 19-1381)
    - H. N. Young (Box-folder 19-1382)
    - W. L. Younger (Box-folder 19-1383)
    - H. H. Zimmerly (Box-folder 19-1384)
  - Subseries 26: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1936-1938
    - Miscellaneous B, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1385)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1386)
    - A. W. Drinkard, 1937 (Box-folder 19-1387)
    - Miscellaneous E,F, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1388)
    - Miscellaneous G, H, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1389)
    - B. L. Hummel, 1937 (Box-folder 19-1390)
    - Miscellaneous I, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1391)
    - J.A. Johnston, 1937 (Box-folder 19-1392)
    - T. W. Knote, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1393)
    - Miscellaneous L, M, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1394)
    - E. C. Magill, 1937 (Box-folder 19-1395)
    - E. C. Miller, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1396)
    - C. M. Newman, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1397)
    - E. B. Norris, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1398)
    - Miscellaneous O, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1399)
    - O'Shaughnessy, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1400)
      - Letter announcing opening day of Mountain Lake Hotel, June 1, 1937
      - Letter regarding first student as a result of the Pan-American Union to allow students from South and Central American countries
      - Letter from the Dean of Engineering regarding a "very strained" relationship between technical departments and the Commandant of Cadets
      - House Resolution 4206: "To aid in furnishing training in flying at several land-grant colleges, and for other purposes"
    - Peery, Gov. George C., 1937 (Box-folder 19-1401)
      - Overcrowded dining hall; increase in student enrollment
    - Price, H. L., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 19-1402)
      - Need for horticulture building
    - Price, J. H., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1403)
    - Priddy, L., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1404)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1405)
    - Rasche, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 19-1406)
    - Redd, H. B., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 19-1407)
    - Robeson, F. L., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1408)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1409)
    - Miscellaneous T, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1410)
    - Tate, M. T., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1411)
    - Tenney, C. H., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1412)
    - Miscellaneous U, V, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1413)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 19-1414)
    - Williams, Dean J. E., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 19-1415)
    - Wilson, I. D., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 20-1416)
      - Annual activity report for VPI Co-operative Wildlife Research Station
      - Harold H. Bailey, naturalist--collector of birds and mammals donation to VPI along with rare book library
    - Woolwine, C. R., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 20-1417)
    - YMCA, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 20-1418)
    - Young, H. N., 1936-1938 (Box-folder 20-1419)
    - Younger, W. L.,, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 20-1420)
    - Zimmerly, H. H., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 20-1421)
  - Subseries 27: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1939
    - Miscellaneous A, B, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1422)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1423)
    - Cochran, J.H., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1424)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1424)
    - Miscellaneous E, F, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1426)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1427)
    - Ganett, W.E., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1428)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1429)
    - Hodges, L., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1430)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1431)
    - Miscellaneous J, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1432)
    - Jeffries, M., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1433)
    - Kinnear, D. L., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1434)
    - Knote, T. W., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1435)
    - Miscellaneous L, M, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1436)
    - Magill, E. C., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1437)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1438)
    - Norris, E.B., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1439)
    - Miscellaneous O, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1440)
    - O'Shaughnessy, L., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1441)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1442)
    - Price, H.L, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1443)
    - Price, Gov. James H., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1444)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1445)
    - Rasche, W. H., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1446)
    - Redd, H. B., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1447)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1448)
    - Seitz, C., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1449)
    - Vilbrandt, F., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1450)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1451)
    - Wade, C., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1452)
    - Wallace, M., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1453)
    - Watson, J., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1454)
    - Woolwine, C., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1455)
    - Miscellaneous Y, 1939 (Box-folder 20-1456)
    - Zimmerly, H. H., 1939 (Box-folder 20-1457)
      - The First Inter-American Student Congress, Cuba, 1939
      - United Student Peace Committee
  - Subseries 28: Miscellaneous Correspondence (includes 1937-1944), 1941-1944
    - Miscellaneous A, B, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1458)
    - Barringer, J. M., Jr., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 20-1459)
    - Bradford, J. H., 1941-1943 (Box-folder 20-1460)
    - Brown, R. M., 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1461)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1462)
    - Cochran, J.H, 1940-41 (Box-folder 20-1463)
    - Cothern, L.I., 1941 (Box-folder 20-1464)
    - Cowgill, C. H., 1941 (Box-folder 20-1465)
    - Derring, Paul N., 1941-44 (Box-folder 20-1466)
    - Drinkard, A.W., 1941-44 (Box-folder 20-1467)
    - Duke, Charles J., Jr., 1942 (Box-folder 20-1468)
    - Miscellaneous E, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1470)
    - Egger, Rowland, 1942 (Box-folder 20-1471)
    - Ellis, W.T., 1940-44 (Box-folder 20-1472)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1473)
    - Fogleman, J.B., 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1474)
    - Miscellaneous G, H, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 20-1475)
    - Harrison, M.C., 1944 (Box-folder 20-1476)
    - Henderson, A.A., 1941-43 (Box-folder 20-1477)
    - Holdaway, C.W., 1943 (Box-folder 20-1478)
    - Holden, R.J., 1940-43 (Box-folder 21-1479)
    - Humbert, R.L., 1941-1942 (2 folders) (Box-folder 21-1480 and 21-1480A)
      - Education's contribution to solution of regional and national problems
    - Hunt, R.E., 1943-44 (Box-folder 21-1481)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., 1940-43 (Box-folder 21-1482)
    - Johnson, W. C., Jr., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1483)
    - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1941-43 (Box-folder 21-1484)
    - Kelsey, V., 1940-1943 (Box-folder 21-1485)
    - Knote, T.W., 1943 (Box-folder 21-1486)
    - Miscellaneous L, M, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1487)
    - McNeil, R.H., 1941 (Box-folder 21-1488)
      - Proposed Education for Women bulletin
    - Miles, Dean C.P., 1944 (Box-folder 21-1489)
    - Miller, E.C., 1940-43 (Box-folder 21-1490)
    - Minter, S.R., 1941 (Box-folder 21-1491)
    - Murray, W.A., 1941 (Box-folder 21-1492)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1493)
    - Norris, E.B., 1940-41 (Box-folder 21-1494)
      - Study of freshman low grades
    - Norton, Paul T. Jr., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1495)
    - Miscellaneous O, P, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1496)
    - Price, H.L., 1940-41 (Box-folder 21-1497)
      - Project summary outline of Virginia Cooperative Wildlife
    - Miscellaneous R, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1498)
    - Rasche, W.H., 1941-1942 (Box-folder 21-1499)
    - Redd, H.B., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1500)
    - Robertson, Senator A. Willis, 1940 (Box-folder 21-1501)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1502)
    - Sanders, H.W., 1941-1942 (Box-folder 21-1503)
    - Seitz, C.E., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1504)
    - Miscellaneous T, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1505)
    - Tate, Mildred T., 1941-1942 (Box-folder 21-1506)
    - Miscellaneous V, W, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21-1507)
    - Wright, J. H., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1508)
    - Young, H.N., 1941 (Box-folder 21-1509)
    - Younger, W.L., 1940-41 (Box-folder 21-1510)
    - Zimmerly, H. H., 1942 (Box-folder 21-1511)
  - Subseries 29: Miscellaneous Files Covering Broad Periods
    - A Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1512)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1513)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1928-42 (Box-folder 21-1514)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1515)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1930-43 (Box-folder 21-1516)
    - F Miscellaneous, 1930-44 (Box-folder 21-1517)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1928-42 (Box-folder 21-1518)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1519)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1928-35 (Box-folder 21-1520)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1929-43 (Box-folder 21-1521)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1929-43 (Box-folder 21-1522)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1523)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1929-43 (Box-folder 21-1524)
    - Mc Miscellaneous, 1929-43 (Box-folder 21-1525)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1929-43 (Box-folder 21-1526)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1928-40 (Box-folder 21-1527)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1928-42 (Box-folder 21-1528)
    - R Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1529)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1530)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1531)
    - Teaching Report, 1938 (Box-folder 21-1532)
      - Report on "major issues of teacher education"
    - U Miscellaneous, 1928-41 (Box-folder 21-1533)
    - V Miscellaneous, 1928-39 (Box-folder 21-1534)
    - W Miscellaneous, 1928-43 (Box-folder 21-1535)
    - X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1928-42 (Box-folder 21-1536)
- Series 4: Subject Files
  - Subseries 1: Physical Plant, 1922-1929
    - S.B. Bennington & Son Contractors, 1924-26 (Box-folder 22-1537)
    - Bids - Heating, 1926 (Box-folder 22-1538)
    - Bids & Prospective Bidders, 1929 (Box-folder 22-1539)
    - Carneal Johnston, Architecture & Engineering, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 22-1540)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Corr Regarding War Memorial, 1924-1929 (Box-folder 22-1541)
      - War Memorial building prints
    - Carneal & Johnston, Remodeling Science Hall, 1927 (Box-folder 22-1551)
    - Carneal & Johnston, 1925 (Box-folder 22-1542)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Re: Dormitory #1, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 22-1543)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Chemistry Building #1, 1927 (Box-folder 22-1544)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Chemistry Building #2, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 22-1545)
    - Carneal & Johnston Copies of Orders, etc., 1925-27 (Box-folder 22-1546)
    - C &J, Copies of Orders to Contractors & etc. #1, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 22-1547)
    - C &J, Copies of Orders to Contractors & etc. #2, 1927 (Box-folder 22-1548)
    - C &J, Copies of Orders to Contractors & etc. #3, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 22-1549)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Copies of Orders, etc., 1926-1927 (Box-folder 22-1550)
    - Carneal & Johnston, Copies of Orders, etc., 1927 (Box-folder 22-1552)
    - Carneal & Johnston-Corr. Regarding Misc. Matters, 1926-29 (Box-folder 22-1553)
    - Carneal & Johnston/Re: Patton Hall, 1925-26 (Box-folder 22-1554)
    - Carneal, Johnston Stone Dormitories, & Patton Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 22-1555)
      - Construction of Patton Engineering Hall
      - Stone dormitory
    - Carneal, Johnston O/S Dorm, & Patton Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 22-1556)
    - Stone Dormitory & Patton Hall (Box-folder 22-1557)
    - Carneal & Johnston Orders - Patton Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 22-1558)
    - Carneal & Johnston Patton Engineering Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1559)